A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3; 636.07 Cubic Feet 1659 containers - 1591 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
  - International Relations, 1962-1976; 14; 31.72 Cubic Feet 55 letter document boxes and 23 legal document boxes
    - Countries/Continents, 2
      - Indonesia (Box 837, Folder 3)
      - Israel - America-Israel Cultural Foundation (Box 837, Folder 4)
      - Israel (Box 838, Folder 1)
      - Japan - A-J (Box 838, Folder 2-4)
      - Japan - J-Z (Box 839, Folder 1-3)
      - Japan - Japan-American Societies (Box 839, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - A-B (Box 839, Folder 5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - C-N (Box 840, Folder 1-4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - O-Z (Box 841, Folder 1-3)
      - Japan Society - By-Laws (Box 841, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Executive Directorship (Box 842, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Board of Directors (Box 842, Folder 2)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions (Miscellaneous) - A-Z (Box 842, Folder 3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions - Rockefeller (Box 842, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions - Intellectual Interchange Program (Box 843, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Dinners, Luncheons, Receptions - A-Z (Box 843, Folder 2-3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Dinners - Annual Dinners (Box 844, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Dinners - Emperor Hirohito and Empress Nagako (Box 844, Folder 2)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Dinners - Miki, Takeo (Box 844, Folder 3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Ford Foundation (Box 844, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Fund Raising (Box 844, Folder 5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House (Box 845, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - A-Z (Box 845, Folder 2)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Architectural Agreement (Plans, Surveys, Borings, Demolition) (Box 845, Folder 3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Building Committee (Box 845, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Early Investigation - Feasibility (Box 846, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Fund Raising (Box 846, Folder 2)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 846, Folder 3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Fund Raising - Federation of Economic Organizations (Box 846, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Ground Breaking Ceremonies (Box 846, Folder 5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Opening (Box 847, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Legal Papers - Property Acquisition (Box 847, Folder 2-3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Printed Material (Box 847, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Donald H. McLean, Jr. materials (Box 847, Folder 5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Overton, Douglas W. (Box 848, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Japan House - Printed Material (Box 848, Folder 2-5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Program Study Committee (Box 849, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Releases (Box 849, Folder 2)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Reports (Box 849, Folder 3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Review Committee (Box 849, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Isaac Shapiro (Box 849, Folder 5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - James L. Stewart (Box 849, Folder 6)
      - Japan - Japan Society - United States-Japan Conferences on Cultural and Educational Interchange, 1962-1963 (Box 850, Folder 1)
      - Korea (Box 849, Folder 7)
      - Nigeria (Box 849, Folder 8)
      - Pakistan (Box 849, Folder 9)
      - Philippines (Box 866, Folder 3)
      - South America (Box 866, Folder 4)
      - Thailand (Box 866, Folder 5)
      - U.S.S.R. (Box 866, Folder 6, Box 867, Folder 1)
      - Venezuela (Box 877, Folder 2)
      - Venezuela - Romulo Betancourt Luncheon, 1963 February 22 (Box 877, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Aid, 3
      - Foreign Aid (Box 830, Folder 1)
      - Biafran Aid Projects (Box 830, Folder 2)
      - Care, Inc. (Box 830, Folder 3)
      - Care/Medico (Box 830, Folder 4)
      - Community Development Foundation, Inc. (Box 830, Folder 5, Box 831, Folder 1)
      - Overseas Development Council (Box 831, Folder 2)
      - Overseas Development Council - Printed Material (Box 831, Folder 3)
      - Oxfam America, Inc. (Box 831, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy, 4
      - Foreign Policy (Box 832, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - A-M (Box 832, Folder 2-4)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - N-Z (Box 833, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Board of Trustees (Box 833, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Bundy, William P. (re. appointment as Editor of Foreign Affairs) (Box 833, Folder 3, Box 834, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions (Box 833, Folder 4, Box 834, Folder 2-3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Miscellaneous Contributions (Box 834, Folder 4)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Fund Raising (Box 835, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 835, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Japan: Its Role in the World Today - Discussion Group (Box 835, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Young, Kenneth T. - The Overseas Chinese and U.S. Policy (Box 835, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Policy Association (Box 835, Folder 5)
      - Foreign Policy Association/World Affairs Center - Contributions (Box 836, Folder 1)
    - Pan American, 5
      - Pan-American - A-P (Box 850, Folder 2-3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations (Box 851, Folder 1-3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - A-Z (Box 851, Folder 4, Box 852, Folder 1-2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Annual Report (Box 852, Folder 3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Art Gallery (Box 853, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Board of Directors (Box 853, Folder 2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Board of Directors - A-Z (Box 853, Folder 3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Building (Box 854, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - John M. Cates, Jr. (Box 854, Folder 2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Commission on U.S.-Latin American Relations (Box 854, Folder 3, Box 855, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Miscellaneous Contributions (Box 855, Folder 2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Rockefeller Family (Box 855, Folder 3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Dinners, Luncheons, Receptions (Box 855, Folder 4)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Dinner, 1972 May 22 (Box 856, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Fund Raising (Box 856, Folder 2-3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - A-Z (Box 857, Folder 1-4, Box 858, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Furnishings (Box 858, Folder 2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Members (Box 858, Folder 3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Printed material (Box 858, Folder 4-5)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Programs (Box 859, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - House of the America's Proposal (Box 859, Folder 2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Public Relations (Box 859, Folder 3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Building Photos (Box 859, Folder 4)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations - Study Papers (Box 860, Folder 1-3)
    - Peace, 6
      - Peace - A-C (Box 860, Folder 4-5)
      - Peace - C-N (Box 861, Folder 1-4)
      - Peace - O-Z (Box 862, Folder 1-4)
      - Bilderberg Meetings (Box 863, Folder 1)
      - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Box 863, Folder 2)
      - Citizen's Exchange Corp. (Box 863, Folder 3)
      - Council on World Tensions (Box 863, Folder 4)
      - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 864, Folder 1)
      - Fund for Peace (Box 864, Folder 2)
      - Fund for Peace - Contributions (Box 864, Folder 3)
      - Negotiations Now (National Committee for a Political Settlement in Vietnam) (Box 864, Folder 4)
      - Philatelic Crusade for Peace (Box 864, Folder 5)
      - Peace Corps (Box 865, Folder 1)
      - SANE (National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy and NY Council for a Sane Nuclear Policy) (Box 865, Folder 2)
      - Strategy for Peace Conference (Box 865, Folder 3)
      - Student Forum on International Order and World Peace (Box 865, Folder 4)
      - United World Federalists (Box 865, Folder 5)
      - World Peace Through Law Center (Box 865, Folder 6)
      - Student Forum Peace Education Center (Box 866, Folder 1)
      - World Peace Study Mission (Box 866, Folder 2)
    - United Nations, 7
      - United Nations - A-U (Box 867, Folder 2-4)
      - United Nations - U-Z (Box 868, Folder 1-2)
      - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (Box 868, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Area Planning (Box 868, Folder 4)
      - Hospitality Committee for U.N. Delegations (Box 868, Folder 5)
      - Printed Material (Box 868, Folder 6)
      - United Nations Association of New York (Box 869, Folder 1)
      - United Nations Association of the USA (Box 869, Folder 2)
      - United Nations Association of the USA - Printed Material (Box 869, Folder 3)
      - United Nations Association of the USA - David Rockefeller (Box 869, Folder 4)
      - United Nations Association of the USA - JDR 3rd (Box 870, Folder 1)
      - United Nations Association of the USA - JDR 3rd - International Cooperation Year (Box 870, Folder 2)
      - United Nations Conference on the Human Environment (Box 870, Folder 3-4)
      - United Nations Development Program (Box 870, Folder 5)
      - United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund (Box 871, Folder 1)
      - United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund - Printed Material (Box 871, Folder 2)
      - United Nations International School (Box 871, Folder 3)
      - United Nations International School - Rockefeller Family (Box 871, Folder 4)
      - United Nations International School - LSR/Smith/Wirth (Box 872, Folder 1)
      - United Nations We Believe (Box 872, Folder 2)
      - World Youth Assembly (Box 872, Folder 3)
    - United States Government, 8
      - United States Government (USG) (Box 872, Folder 4)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) (Box 872, Folder 5-6, Box 873, Folder 1)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - A-Z (Box 873, Folder 2-3)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Clippings (Box 873, Folder 4)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Press Kit (Box 873, Folder 5)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - By-Laws (Box 874, Folder 1)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Board of Directors (Box 874, Folder 2)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Contributions (Box 874, Folder 3)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Countries (Box 874, Folder 4)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Fund Raising (Box 874, Folder 5)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Letters of Commendation (Box 875, Folder 1)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Printed material (Box 875, Folder 2-3)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Reports (Box 875, Folder 4-5)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Staff (Box 875, Folder 6)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Volunteers (Box 876, Folder 1)
      - Department of State (Box 876, Folder 2)
      - Department of State - Fine Arts Committee (Box 876, Folder 3-4, Box 877, Folder 1)
  - J-M, 1962-1976; 15; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
    - J - Miscellaneous (Box 877, Folder 4)
    - K - Miscellaneous (Box 877, Folder 5-6)
    - L - Miscellaneous (Box 878, Folder 1-2)
    - Lawhorn, Shields (Box 878, Folder 3)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - A-Z (Box 878, Folder 4, Box 879, Folder 1-4, Box 880, Folder 1-3, Box 881, Folder 1-2)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - Addresses (Box 881, Folder 3)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - Building Owners' and Managers' Association of Greater NY (Box 881, Folder 4)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - Clippings (Box 882, Folder 1)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - Manitoba - The Interlake Area Development Plan (Box 882, Folder 2)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - Rockefeller University (Box 882, Folder 3-4)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - United States Government - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box 883, Folder 1)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - Wall Street Club (Box 883, Folder 2)
    - Lindquist, Warren T. - White House Conference on Aging (Box 883, Folder 3-4, Box 884, Folder 1)
    - M - Miscellaneous (Box 884, Folder 2-3, Box 885, Folder 1)
  - Medicine, 1962-1976; 16; 31.9 Cubic Feet 84 letter document boxes
    - Medicine - A-Z, 1
      - Medicine - A (Box 885, Folder 2-4)
      - Medicine - A-C (Box 886, Folder 1-4)
      - Medicine - C-G (Box 887, Folder 1-5)
      - Medicine - H-K (Box 888, Folder 1-4)
      - Medicine - L-M (Box 889, Folder 1-4)
      - Medicine - M-N (Box 890, Folder 1-3)
      - Medicine - O-R (Box 891, Folder 1-3)
      - Medicine - S-T (Box 892, Folder 1-4)
      - Medicine - U-Z (Box 893, Folder 1-2)
      - African Medical and Research Foundation (Box 893, Folder 3)
      - Air Pollution (Box 893, Folder 4)
      - Alcoholism (Box 894, Folder 1)
      - Alcoholism - National Council on Alcoholism (Box 894, Folder 2)
      - American Cancer Society (Box 894, Folder 3)
      - American Cancer Society - New York City Cancer Committee (Box 894, Folder 4)
      - American Cancer Society - Miscellaneous Chapters (Box 895, Folder 1-2)
      - American Cancer Society - New York City Division, Inc. (Box 895, Folder 3)
      - American Health Foundation (Box 895, Folder 4)
        formerly Environmental Health Foundation
      - American Cancer Society - New York City Division - Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. Memorial Award Dinner, 1971 (Box 896, Folder 1)
      - Arthritis Foundation, Inc. (Box 896, Folder 2)
      - Bethesda National Foundation Cancer Care, Inc. (Box 896, Folder 3)
      - Cancer Care, Inc. (Box 896, Folder 4)
      - China Medical Board of New York (Box 897, Folder 1)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York (Box 897, Folder 2,4, Box 898, Folder 1)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - American Red Cross of Greater NY (Box 897, Folder 3, Box 898, Folder 2)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - Contributions (Box 898, Folder 3)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - Miscellaneous Contributions (Box 899, Folder 1)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - Fundraising (Box 899, Folder 2)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - New York Blood Center and Affiliated Blood Research Institute (Box 899, Folder 3)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - New York Blood Center - Printed material (Box 899, Folder 4)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - Printed Material (Box 899, Folder 5, Box 900, Folder 1)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - Rockefeller, David Appeal Letters (Box 900, Folder 2)
      - Community Blood Council of Greater New York - Rockefeller, Laurance Appeal, 1964 (Box 900, Folder 3-4)
      - Foundations (Box 900, Folder 5)
      - Foundations - Arthritis Foundation (Box 901, Folder 2)
      - Foundations - Allergy Foundation of America (Box 901, Folder 2)
      - Foundations - Thomas A. Dooley Foundation (Box 901, Folder 3)
      - Foundations - Foundation for Research of the New York Academy of Osteopathy (Box 901, Folder 4)
      - Foundations - Joslin Diabetes Foundation (Box 901, Folder 5)
      - Foundations - Mayo Foundation (Box 901, Folder 6)
      - Foundations - National Foundation (Box 901, Folder 7)
      - Health Policy Advisory Center (Box 902, Folder 1)
      - Jackson Laboratory (Box 902, Folder 2)
      - Martin, Daniel S. (Dr.) (Box 902, Folder 3)
      - Mount Desert Island Biological Lab (Box 902, Folder 4)
      - National Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 903, Folder 1)
      - New York Association of Brain Injured Children (Box 903, Folder 2)
      - Pan-American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools (Box 903, Folder 3)
      - United Cerebral Palsy Association (Box 903, Folder 4)
      - United Cerebral Palsy Association - New York City Committee (Box 903, Folder 5)
      - Water Pollution (Box 967, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals, 2
      - Hospitals - A-C (Box 904, Folder 1-3)
      - Hospitals - C-H (Box 905, Folder 1-4)
      - Hospitals - H-L (Box 906, Folder 1-4)
      - Hospitals - M (Box 907, Folder 1-3)
      - Hospitals - M-O (Box 908, Folder 1-3)
      - Hospitals - P-R (Box 909, Folder 1-4)
      - Hospitals - S-Z (Box 910, Folder 1-3)
      - American Colonies Charities Association, Inc. (Box 910, Folder 4)
      - American Medical Center for Burma (Box 910, Folder 5)
      - American Hospital in Paris (Box 911, Folder 1)
      - American Research Hospital in Poland (Box 911, Folder 2)
      - Arkansas Baptist Hospital (Box 911, Folder 3)
      - Bellevue Hospital (Center) (Box 911, Folder 4)
      - Children's Hospital Medical Center (Box 911, Folder 5)
      - Children's Hospital of Michigan (Box 911, Folder 6)
      - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center (Box 911, Folder 7)
      - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center Fund (Box 912, Folder 1)
      - Addis Ababa Fistula Hospital (Box 912, Folder 2)
      - Hospital for Special Surgery (Box 912, Folder 3)
      - Knox County General Hospital (Box 912, Folder 4)
      - Lenox Hill Hospital (Box 912, Folder 5)
      - Maine Coast Memorial Hospital (Box 912, Folder 6)
      - Mary Hitchcock Memorial Hospital (Box 912, Folder 7)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - A-C (Box 913, Folder 1-4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - D-I (Box 914, Folder 1-3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - I-N (Box 915, Folder 1-4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - O-Z (Box 916, Folder 1-4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Air Rights (Box 917, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Annual Reports (Box 917, Folder 2-3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Articles (Box 917, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Belmont Ball (Box 917, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Board of Trustees (Box 918, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Centralized Hospital Laundry (Box 918, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Clippings (Box 918, Folder 3, Box 919, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions (Box 919, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 919, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions - Miscellaneous - A-Z (Box 919, Folder 4, Box 920, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions - Miscellaneous - Helen H. Brown (Box 920, Folder 2-3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Coombe, Reginald C. (Box 920, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Directory (Officers and Board Members) (Box 920, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Dedication of New Hospital (Box 921, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Finances (Box 921, Folder 2-4, Box 922, Folder 1-4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Finances - Contributions, Bequests and Grants in Cash (Box 923, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Finances - Income Trusts and Bequests (Box 923, Folder 3, Box 924, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Legal (Box 923, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Finances - Investment Advisory Accounts (Box 924, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Finances - Joint Committee on Financial Policy (Box 925, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Pediatric Pavilion Children's Solarium (Box 925, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Status of Capital Program (Box 925, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Finances - Summary Financial Information (Box 926, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Fund Raising (Box 927, Folder 1-3, Box 926, Folder 2-3, Box 928, Folder 1-2, Box 929, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Fund Raising - G.A. Brakeley & Company (Box 929, Folder 2-3, Box 930, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Fund Raising - Building Fund Committee (Box 930, Folder 2-3, Box 931, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Fund Raising - Luncheons (Box 931, Folder 2-3, Box 932, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Joint Staff Conference Committee (Box 931, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Luncheons - LSR Luncheon, 1976 October 6 (Box 932, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings/Minutes - Annual Meetings (Box 932, Folder 3-4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings/Minutes - Board of Trustee Minutes (Box 933, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings/Minutes - Executive Committee (Box 933, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings/Minutes - Miscellaneous Committees (Box 933, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Meetings/Minutes - Committee on Scientific Policy Minutes (Box 933, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Merger (Box 933, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - New Hospital Building (Box 934, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Printed Material (Box 934, Folder 2-3, Box 935, Folder 1-3, Box 936, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Printed Material - Center News (Box 936, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Printed Material - Clinical Bulletin (Box 937, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Public Relations (Box 937, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Real Estate and Planning Committee (Box 937, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Releases (Box 937, Folder 4, Box 938, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Rockefeller, Laurance S. Notes (Box 938, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Search Committee (Box 938, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Search for President (Box 938, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Senior Staff, 1967-1971 (Box 939, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Staff (A-L), 1965-1976 (Box 939, Folder 2)
        Retricted - Personnel - Open in 2046
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Staff (M-S), 1965-1976 (Box 939, Folder 3)
        Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2046
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Staff (T-Z), 1965-1976 (Box 940, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Staff - VP of Finance search, 1976 (Box 940, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Staff Pension Trust Funds, 1966-1968 (Box 940, Folder 3)
        Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2038
      - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center - Staff - Dr. Lewis Thomas, 1973-1974 (Box 940, Folder 4)